I can't understand why you feel this way!
How can you say that you
love Masamune-sama, then?
Did you know?
He used to be a bit weird and different, too.
Even if he dislikes me or denies me,
I won't let Masamune go now.
Because...
that's just who I am.
So... I'm in the same boat as you.
Our feelings only go one way.
I think my feelings might be
more deeply rooted, though.
Man, it's cold.
#10 "Whiteout"
Yoshino.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's cold, so let's get something to eat.
A café, a family restaurant, or a
sweets parlor? Where should we go?
Aki-sama...
Has something happened?
Not really.
You're lying.
I just had a little conversation.
I was told that Makabe doesn't
really have feelings for me,
and that I should break up with him...
by Commando girl.
Stop that, Yoshino!
But Aki-sama, that's so cruel!
What she said wasn't exactly wrong, though.
It's true that he doesn't love me.
He only got close to me because he hates me.
No...
That's not true, Aki-sama!
Yoshino?
You've completely got the wrong idea.
It's all my fault. I did this.
I'm so sorry...
You two aren't at fault here.
I...
hated Pig's Foot so much, and I didn't
want him to take you from me...
That's why I called him
"Pig's Foot
and chased him off.
Apparently, Pig's Foot transferred
to our school to get revenge.
But I didn't want him to do that.
That's why I pretended to help him, but I
was going to try to help you two make up.
So you worked really hard.
Please don't say that he doesn't love you.
The feelings between you
and Pig's Foot are mutual.
Pig's Foot knows that, too.
Oh, you're so...
No. You two are so...
You'll get wet.
Say, there's something
I want you to look into.
Whoa.
It really piled up.
Wow, that's amazing!
It's been forever since we got this much snow!
Let's make a snowman!
Nope, not happening.
Huh? Why not?
It's cold, it's too much trouble, and it's cold.
Boo. Fine, then. I'll make one myself.
You just stay and sulk in the warm
house, Grandpa Party Pooper.
Grandpa?!
Don't you dare underestimate my muscles!
Hup, hup, hup, hup, hup, hup!
Wow! That's the spirit, Onii-chan!
Should we use buttons for its eyes?
Wait, leave this to me.
There, all done.
Wait, wait, that's terrifying!
Why is it a Daruma doll?!
Well, a snowman is technically
called "yukidaruma," right?
Ah...
It's good luck, too. This is one of my best.
Huh... Who are you sending that to?
Your girlfriend?
Wh-Why does that matter?
Hey, when are you going to let me
meet this supposed girlfriend of yours?
What?
Mom said she wants to meet her, too.
Oh! Why don't we invite her
over this weekend?
Huh?! No way!
Boo... I just want to be friends
with your girlfriend.
Well, eventually...
Really?! You better!
Oh, jeez. All right already.
White Day is next week.
Man, I can't wait to get all those return gifts.
Right?
Man, every single year! That pressure!
All because we accepted
chocolates on Valentine's Day...
Even if it was obligatory!
Why did you do that?
If I said it was for
Masamune-sama's happiness...
Would ya think I'm oversteppin' my bounds?
Huh?
Is being hurt, pushing yourself too hard,
and lying to yourself really what love is?
No one can attain happiness from that.
That includes Aki-sama, of course.
Fujinomiya-san...
I don't really understand, but...
To them, I'm sure I'm a villain.
But...
That's fine. That's perfectly fine.
I wonder why she wants to know about this...
Man, I'm full.
I am, too. What a lovely meal.
What, already?!
W-Well, I was too hungry
earlier, so I already ate...
Oh, okay.
Yeah, there's no way you'd be
satisfied with just five breads.
Oh, shut up!
Oh, right. Did you see that
photo I sent this morning?
Oh, of the snowman?
Didn't that look awesome?
Ah... I just thought you had a lot of
time on your hands in the morning.
D'oh! That's so mean!
I'm kidding. You must be
really close to your little sister.
Thanks for sending me this.
So, hey... If you have time sometime...
N-No, never mind!
Don't worry about it!
Oh, just spit it out already.
I'll tell you some other time.
Fine, I'll wait. But I won't get my hopes up.
Fujinomiya-san!
Kojuurou-sama, did you need something?
U-Um...
Why don't we walk home together?
It's actually quite nice walking
home every once in a while.
O-Oh, right. You usually
get a ride to and from school.
Sorry to ask you to do this on short notice.
It's perfectly fine.
You can be much harsher
with me if you'd like.
Considering what I did, it wouldn't be
unexpected for you to despise me.
D-Despise you?!
Don't say that! I'd never
feel that way about you!
Sure, I was a little surprised,
but I was just worried about you.
I still don't regret what I said to Aki-sama...
But I'd be lying if I said
that I didn't feel guilty.
It doesn't appear as though Aki-sama
and Masamune-sama have broken up,
and part of me is relieved by that.
I wonder what I really am.
To me, Fujinomiya-san...
You're a very straightforward
and kind person.
Aki-sama, it's Yoshino.
Come in.
I've finished looking into the
thing you asked me about.
Thanks. That must have been rough.
Um...
Yes?
How have things been with
Pig's Foo—I mean, Makabe?
What? Where did that come from?
I-I'm sorry.
It's all right. There's nothing
for you to worry about.
Aki-sama...
Because you told me the truth,
I don't have to doubt him anymore.
And thanks to that, I can now
face him with how I truly feel.
Thanks, Yoshino.
Adagaki Aki
Adagaki-san?
Hello?
Hey, Makabe? Is now a good time?
Sure. What's up?
Do you want to go on a date this weekend?
A da— Adagaki-san is inviting me?!
Sure. I was actually about
to ask you out on one, too.
Really? Great.
White Day is coming up, too.
Who?! Wha— White Day?!
Oh, shit. I had nothing planned.
Uh, wait. I'm... supposed to
give her something back, right?
What do I give her?
Like, how much?
What situation should this be?
Also, Makabe... Are you listening?
I-I'm listening. Of course I'm listening.
White Day what to return to top choice
White Day girlfriend date
White Day recommended shops
White Day recommended presents
Okay, good.
For this date, I'd like you
to let me plan everything.
There's somewhere I'd like to take you.
Ah... Yeah, sure.
Did you want to go shopping?
Well,
something like that.
Yeah? That seems pretty fun.
Perhaps.
Okay, sounds good.
Yes. Goodnight.
Goodnight.
Let's see...
Yeah, you should get her a ring.
A ring?! For White Day?!
Yeah! A ring would be great.
Notion rejected!
Aw, then how about
an electric facial device?
You just want one for yourself.
Nope, she's no help at all.
Well, since she gave you homemade
chocolates for Valentine's Day,
why don't you go all-out and
make something for her, as well?
Huh...
Almond Powder
Cake Flour
Thirty-five grams of egg whites,
thirty grams of granulated sugar,
thirty-five grams of almond powder...
What are you going to make?
What else? Macarons,
since girls like them so much.
What? Really?
Macarons are really hard to make.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah...
Why not try something simpler, like cookies?
Yeah, yeah...
No, I'm going to make macarons.
There's nothing that I can't do!
Are macarons supposed to look like this?
Nope. Not even close.
How about this?
Those are clearly just crackers.
Well played, macarons...
But I will not give up!
Not ever!
I'm going to... bake you up nice and round!
So... you decided to just buy them.
Yeah, I did. Do you know any good places?
Well... What sweets does Adagaki-san like?
Anything that tastes good.
For better or for worse,
Adagaki-san's got a sharp tongue.
She won't be happy unless she gets the best.
Hmm... Then I know the best place.
What?
So cute!
Thank you.
Thanks.
Wow, this is crazy.
I figured there'd be a lot of people.
Why are there so many girls here?
They're probably here for all the
limited-edition White Day sweets.
In some couples, the wife gives
the return gift, not the husband.
Wait, do you always shop at places like this?
For a special treat every now
and then. I love depachikas.
Shortcake
Éclair
Chocolate Millefeuille
Rare cheesecake
Mocha Roll
Millefeuille
Wow!
What a delicious-looking Mont Blanc!
Oh, I guess this is pistachio cake.
Yeah they do look really good.
Pistachio Cake
It's so expensive!
That's standard for high-grade sweets.
Seriously?
Oh, since you're giving it to her
in return for Valentine's Day,
you might want to get something that'll keep.
Like cookies or chocolates.
There are so many. Which one should I get?
White
Day
Fair
Limited
Time
Shop
Limited time?
Apparently, this shop is only here right now.
So cute!
Wow, they're so cute.
They're great.
Yeah.
They are cute.
It seems cheeky, sorta like Adagaki-san.
Okay, I'll take it. May I get this, please?
Thanks for everything today.
You really helped.
It's no big deal.
I hope Adagaki-san likes it.
Yeah.
I see you bought some, too. Are they for you?
Huh?
N-No. I thought I'd give them to Fujinomiya-san.
Huh? Even though you gave
her a Valentine's Day gift?
I did... But after looking at a few of these,
I felt like giving her something.
Well, I guess that's something you'd do.
Oh, hey. Considering what time it is,
why don't we get something to eat?
Good idea. How about ramen?
Ramen at night?
That's so many calories, but I'll go with you.
Yay!
Are you going on a date?
I see you're as sharp as usual.
Enjoying your youth, I see.
Well, I'll see you later.
Yes. Have a wonderful time.
You should enjoy your youth
while you still can, too.
Whatever. I'm not even interested in that.
This is the place, right?
Welcome.
This is obviously just a regular drugstore.
Why did we go to one in the next town?
Hello.
Oh.
Thank goodness.
I thought I had the wrong place.
No, you didn't make a mistake.
This is the place.
Did you need to buy something?
Yes. One sec.
Excuse me.
Yes? How can I help you?
It's been a while. Do you remember me?
Huh?
You went to Higashi Elementary.
When you were little,
you would play near my mansion.
O-Oh! The Adagaki place?
Yes. I'm the only daughter of that family.
And...
you used to bully him.
U-Um...
You don't remember?
Makabe Masamune. Back then,
his name was Hayase Masamune.
Hayase...
Tubbymune?!
Seriously? I didn't recognize you at all!
Uh, yeah.
You're like a totally different guy!
Right? Because he lost an
incredible amount of weight.
Huh, I see.
Hey, Suzuki-kun, are you
done stocking the shelves?
S-Sorry!
Sorry to get in your way.
Anyway, we'll be going now.
Hayase-kun!
Sorry about all that!
Have you calmed down?
Were you planning this from the start?
Yes. How did you feel seeing him?
Were you scared?
No. Surprisingly, I felt fine.
Actually, it didn't even matter.
I thought I'd freak out a little more.
I found out where some of the others
are now. Do you want to see them?
Nah.
I see. I figured.
You're stronger now, Masamune.
You worked really hard, you lost weight,
and you were able to change.
You're okay now.
Have more confidence in yourself.
Come on, stop that. Don't start
crying after everything I just said.
Sorry.
Thank you, Aki-chan.
Um, here.
This isn't exactly to thank you
for just now. It's for White Day.
Really? What's inside?
White chocolate. Sorry it's so unoriginal.
The taste is more important than originality.
I want to touch her... I wonder if I can.
But...
I'm sorry.
I can't accept this.
Huh?
I think it's okay for at least one person to
pick up what you're trying to throw away.
So...
Goodbye, Makabe Masamune-kun.